

# CONTACT

in Mykyta Cherevatyi

@mykyta ch

mykytacherevatyi.com

## **SKILLS**

- JavaScript, TypeScript
- React
- Node.js
- RDMBS (PostgreSQL, Oracle)
- NoSQL (MongoDB)
- APIs (REST)
- Docker, Docker compose
- CI\CD; Jenkins; Kubernetes
- Swagger
- Bitbucket, Git
- Test (Jest)
- Agile

#### LANGUAGES

- English Upper-Intermediate
  (B2)
- Ukrainian native

## **EDUCATION**

2016 - 2021 DNIPRO UNIVERSITY OF TECHNOLOGY

• Bachelor of Cyber security

# MYKYTA CHEREVATYI

# **FULL STACK DEVELOPER**

## **ABOUT ME**

Experienced Web Developer with a demonstrated history of working in the program development industry. Last 5 years I've been working in companies like Lendiron Ltd company and SYTOSS as a full-stack web developer. I create successful responsive websites and services that are fast, easy to use, and are built with best practices.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

#### SYTOSS (Project GUCCI platform)

Sep 2021 - Feb 2024

Full stack developer

- Development of applications for a largest telecommunication company In Austria, which are necessary for agents and clients.
   Development from scratch, design, constant communication with BA's, PO's.
- Tools and Technologies: JavaScript; Typescript; React; Redux; Node.js; Express; Oracle; Jenkins; Kubernetes; Docker; ArgoCD; Backstage;

#### Lendiron (Project Topfinance)

Feb 2021 - Aug 2021

Full stack developer

- FinTech project offers a productive investment opportunity. Developed admin and client sides with complex logic of transactions.
- Tools and Technologies: JavaScript; Typescript; React; Redux; reactquery; Node.js; Express; MySQL;

## **Lendiron (Project Tototheo)**

Jan 2020 - June 2020

Front end developer

- Yacht portal with 3D model of the boat and displaying data from IoT on its decks. Improved design, developed admin and client sides, implemented graphs, flexible tables, forms with validators etc.
- Tools and Technologies: JavaScript, Typescript, React, Redux, Node.js, Express, MySQL

#### **Lendiron** (Project Meisterfit)

Nov 2019 - Jan 2021

Full stack developer

- Mobile application for athletes with the web admin part where coaches can create and assign programs to them. Developed code for web and mobile platforms. Created, improved and fixed API routes written on Express. Set up a system of notifications via emails.
- Tools and Technologies: JavaScript, Typescript, React, Redux, React Native, Node.js, Express, PostgreSQL